<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Omidyar</string>
    <string-array name="country_array">
        <item>Select country</item>
        <item>India</item>
        <item>Australia</item>
        <item>USA</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>Jamaica</item>
        <item>Japan</item>
        <item>Brasil</item>
        <item>England</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="language_array">
        <item>Select language</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Hindi</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="currency_array">
        <item>Select currency</item>
        <item>INR</item>
        <item>USD</item>
        <item>UR</item>
        <item>AUD</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="about_this_app">About This Tool</string>
    <string name="preference_file_key">com.sayone.omidyar.PREFERENCE_FILE_KEY</string>
    <string name="sign_up_button">Sign up</string>
    <string name="login_button">login</string>
    <string name="surveyor_login_button">Surveyor login</string>
    <string name="date_hint">Date</string>
    <string name="respondent_group_hint">Respondent group</string>
    <string name="surveyor_hint">Surveyor</string>
    <string name="community_hint">Community</string>
    <string name="district_hint">District</string>
    <string name="state_hint">State</string>
    <string name="survey_hint">Survey</string>
    <string name="passcode_hint">Passcode</string>
    <string name="admin_login_button">Admin login</string>
    <string name="empty_surveyor_filed">Surveyor cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="empty_community_field">community cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="login_successful">Login Successful</string>
    <string name="login_failed">Login Failed</string>
    <string name="empty_respondent_group">Respondent group cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="empty_state_filed">State cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="empty_district_filed">District cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="empty_country_filed">Select country</string>
    <string name="empty_currency_field">Select currency</string>
    <string name="empty_language_field">Select language</string>
    <string name="registration_success">Registration Successful</string>
    <string name="empty_passcode">Passcode cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="empty_date_filed">Select date</string>
    <string name="about_this_tool_para1">This is a tool intended to assist in community asset valuation, developed by Indufor North America LLC in collaboration with the Foundation for Ecological Security.
    </string>
    <string name="about_this_tool_para2">Millions of the world’s poor inhabit traditional lands and rely on natural resources for their livelihoods. While such lands and resources provide communities with incomes, shelter and food, there is little understanding of the economic value of these community assets within the community or by other stakeholders. The dearth of information on community assets leaves communities vulnerable to speculation and, perhaps, missed opportunities to benefit from their natural capital. When faced with outside interest in their lands or resources, communities find themselves ill equipped to negotiate fair compensation. At the same time, companies and governments create risks to themselves by underestimating the value of community assets. This is increasingly a concern as commercial investment in land and natural resources grows.
    </string>
    <string name="about_this_tool_para3">Some initiatives promoting the integration of natural capital accounting into national wealth accounting attempt to place monetary values on the natural resources in an economy. These initiatives provide some information and guidance to identify the myriad values generated by natural resources. Yet, they generally focus their attention at the macro-level and ignore the values natural resources provide to households and communities. The nascent field of social capital accounting is also likely to provide more information on the value generated through social networks, but to date the link has not been made between strong social capital and natural resource value.
    </string>
    <string name="about_this_tool_para4">Equipping communities, the investment community and governments with a tool to ascertain an economic value on the range of assets (tangible and intangible) held and used by communities might help reduce information asymmetry and empower communities to negotiate from a stronger position thereby reducing conflicts and improving investment outcomes.
    </string>
    <string name="empty_survey_field">Provide survey id</string>
    <string name="survey_absent">survey id doesn\'t exist</string>
</resources>
